Guide to the Earl Casey Accessions
The Wittliff Collections
- Accession 2021-094, 2 Linear Feet; 4 boxes Audio and digital files on cassette tapes and thumb drives; Archival materials received from journalist and former CNN senior vice president, Earl Casey. Casey, a longtime friend of Jerry Jeff and Susan Walker, served as the chief researcher and writer/co
  - Audio Cassettes
    - Interview "Allen Damron 9/7/1990"; Met Jerry Jeff Walker on Jerry's "first trip to Austin". Played Mr. Bojangles, Side A and B. TDK D90 cassette tape, September 7, 1990 (Box 3663, Item 26)
    - Interview "Guy Clark Townes Van Zandt 5/16/88"; Met Jerry Jeff Walker in Houston, mid-sixties, close friends, Side A, Side B portion only. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, May 16, 1988 (Box 3663, Item 27)
    - Interview "Gary White 5/1+2/1987"; Met in Houston, joined Jerry Jeff Walker Lost Sea Dreamers, Circus Maximus Side A and B Austin to Gruen, Texas. Maxell HBII 90 cassette tape, May 1, 1987 (Box 3663, Item 28)
    - Interview "Bob Bruno Takoma Park 3/12/88" Met in Austin, joined Jerry Jeff Walker Lost Sea Dreamers, Circus Maximus, Side A and B. Sony UX 90 cassette tape, March 12, 1988 (Box 3663, Item 29)
    - Interview "Bob Bruno Takoma Park, MD 3/12/88" Met in Austin, joined Jerry Jeff Walker Lost Sea Dreamers, Circus Maximus, Side A, Side B blank. Sony UX 90 cassette tape, March 12, 1988 (Box 3663, Item 30)
    - Interview "Dave Scherstrom 9/7/90" Drummer, Lost Sea Dreamers, Circus Maximus, Side A and B. TDK D90 cassette tape, September 7, 1990 (Box 3663, Item 31)
    - Interview "Kat Walker 1+2 7/22/1988"; Married to Jerry Jeff Walker 1967-1971 catalyst for JJW move to New York, Side A and B. Sony UX 90 cassette tape, July 12, 1988 (Box 3663, Item 32)
    - Interview "Kat Walker 3+4 7/22/1988"; Married to Jerry Jeff Walker 1967-1971 catalyst for JJW move to New York, Side A and B. Sony UX 90 cassette tape, July 12, 1988 (Box 3663, Item 33)
    - Interview "David Bromberg 9/17/90"; Partner, string empresario, played on WBAI Mr. Bojangles, Side A, Side B blank. TDK D90 cassette tape, September 17, 1990 (Box 3663, Item 34)
    - Interview "Nick Holmes NYC"; Met Jerry Jeff Walker >1969 during coffeehouse years, Side A 1, Side B 2. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, July 18, 1987 (Box 3663, Item 35)
    - Interview "Nick Holmes/Bob Fass WBAI"; Side A Nick Holmes/Bob Fass WBAI, Side B Bob Fass, WBAI legendary late night host, recorded Jerry Jeff Walker on-air "Mr. Bojangles". Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, July 18, 1987 (Box 3663, Item 36)
    - Interview "3 WBAI Bob Fass "; Bob Fass, WBAI legendary late night host, recorded Jerry Jeff Walker on-air "Mr. Bojangles", Side A 3, Side B 4. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, July 18, 1987 (Box 3663, Item 37)
    - Interview "3 WBAI Bob Fass "; Bob Fass, WBAI legendary late night host, recorded Jerry Jeff Walker on-air "Mr. Bojangles", Side A 1, Side B 2. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, July 18, 1987 (Box 3663, Item 38)
    - Interview "Paul Sieble 9/6/90"; Met Jerry Jeff Walker in "baskethouse" and coffeehouse days. JJW idol, Side A and B. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, September 6, 1990 (Box 3663, Item 39)
    - Interview "Pat Kenney NYC 9-11-90"; Owner, Kenney's Castaways, NYC. Booked Jerry Jeff Walker in 70s in NY, close friend, Side A, Side B blank, TDK D90 cassette tape, September 11, 1990 (Box 3663, Item 40)
    - Interview "Dan Elliot 9/13/90 NYC 60's": Booker, owner, agent. Met Jerry Jeff Walker and band early Lost Sea Dreamers days NYC, Side A, Side B blank. TDK D90 cassette tape, September 13, 1990 (Box 3663, Item 41)
    - Interview "Sally Ann Mitchell 1 + 2 7-9-90"; Serious Jerry Jeff Walker love figure, 1965. Letters, detail. "Morning Song to Sally", Side A and B. Sony UX-S 90 cassette tape, July 9, 1990 (Box 3663, Item 42)
    - Interview "Sally Ann Mitchell 3 7-9-90"; Serious Jerry Jeff Walker love figure, 1965. Letters, detail. "Morning Song to Sally", Side A, Side B blank. Sony UX-S 90 cassette tape, July 9, 1990 (Box 3663, Item 43)
    - Interview "Rod Kennedy 8/22/90"; Met Jerry Jeff Walker before Circus Maximus, 11th door, Chequered Flag. Side A and B Austin 60's, Kerryville Folkfest (See Also Alan Damron, Segle Fry). Maxwell XLII 90 cassette tape, August 22, 1990 (Box 3663, Item 44)
    - Interview "Utah Phillips/Ramblin' Jack 3-18-90"; Phillips performer, historian, much background on evolution of folk-country. Ramblin' Jack Elliot, legend. Knew Jerry Jeff Walker NYC and Early Dallas-Austin, Side A, Side B blank. Maxwell UDII 90 cassette tape, March 18, 1990 (Box 3663, Item 45)
    - Interview "Jay Vurhultz [sic] 8-9-90 Austin Years"; Late 1964, first met Jerry Jeff Walker at the Id, New Orleans and 11th Door, Side A and B. Maxwell XLII 90 cassette tape, August 9, 1990 (Box 3663, Item 46)
    - Interview "Pat Verhultz 8-9-90 (Austin years: See Jay Verhultz)"; Former wife of Jay Verhultz, early Austin details, Side A and B, Maxwell XLII 90 cassette tape, August 9, 1990 (Box 3663, Item 47)
    - Interview "-JJW + Michael Martin Murphy -Michael Martin Murphy"; Side A Jerry Jeff Walker and Murphy McDonald's Memories, Side B Murphy great detail on early Austin era. Maxwell XLII 90 cassette tape, December 30, 1987 (Box 3663, Item 48)
    - Interview "Michael Martin Murphy"; Side A Taos, great detail on early Austin era, Side B blank. TDK D90 cassette tape, December 30, 1987 (Box 3663, Item 49)
    - Interview "Ray Wylie Hubbard"; Singer-songwriter, wrote Redneck Mother, Side A, Side B blank. TDK D90 cassette tape, October 2, 1990 (Box 3663, Item 50)
    - Interview "Gary P. Nunn"; Lost Gonzo Band, Jan 1972 with Michael Martin Murphy. "London Homesick Blues", Side A and B. Maxwell XLII 90 cassette tape, December 17, 1988 (Box 3663, Item 51)
    - Interview "Craig Hillis 8/24/90"; Lost Gonzo Band, Jan 1972 with Michael Martin Murphy, Side A and B. Maxwell XLII 90 cassette tape, August 24, 1990 (Box 3663, Item 52)
    - Interview "John Inmon 12/16/88"; Lost Gonzo Band, guitar impresario, Austin: Steamboat Springs Side A and B. Memorex dBS 90 cassette tape, December 16, 1988 (Box 3663, Item 53)
    - Interview "Freddy KRC"; Steady Freddy, drummer, singer. Brief story told. Side A "Freddy Kirk: The Vegas Move 8/20/90"; Side B blank. Maxell XLII 90, August 20, 1990 (Box 3663, Item 54)
    - Interview "Eddie Wilson"; Armadillo World Headquarters founder, Jerry Jeff Walker memory, some critical, Side A and B. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, August 22, 1990 (Box 3663, Item 55)
    - Interview "Steve Fromholtz 12-15-88"; Wild man, Texas State student with Michael Martin Murphy, great history '69+. Side A and B. Maxell XLII 90 cassette tape, December 15, 1988 (Box 3663, Item 56)
    - Interview "Walt Garrison 9/27/90"; Rodeo icon, very brief knockdown story, Side A, Side B blank. TDK D90 cassette tape, September 27, 1990 (Box 3663, Item 57)
    - Liquid Lace (An Opus): memoirs of a Self-Proclaimed Romantic - Photocopied manuscript of unpublished autobiography of Ben Jennings, good friend of Jerry Jeff Walker. Pp. 1-216 and 6 pages of photos. RESTRICTED UNTIL 2035 WITHOUT CURATOR OR DIRECTOR'S PERMISSION, undated (Box 3664, Folder 1)